couponingfor4.net 2014-11-18

# Privacy Policy

_This post may contain affiliate links. Read my disclosure policy[here](http://www.couponingfor4.net/disclosure-policy/)_.

This privacy policy applies to my website – Couponing For 4: http://www.couponingfor4.net/

I highly value your privacy and will make this policy easily available throughout my site to assist you in understanding the handling of information in the course of using this site.

Log Files and Cookies

This website utilizes industry standard analytics packages which gathers limited information on visitors to my website automatically, and stores this anonymous information in server log files. This information may include IP addresses, browser type, basic IP information, referring pages, operating system used and date/time stamps. This information does not identify individual users; it is used only for site administration, as well as for analysis of website usage and trends.

With respect to Ad Servers

To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, I have relationships with other companies like PubAccess (www.Advertising.com ) that I allow to place ads on my Web page. As a result of your visit to my site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address, browser used, interest categories based on information collected from web surfing habits, or if you have Flash installed and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policy of:

http://www.google.com/privacy.html

I use third-party companies to serve ads and collect non-personally identifiable information ( _e.g.,_ the pages you visit, and which links you click, which ads you see and click on, and the categories of search terms you enter) when you visit our web site. These companies may use the information outlined above (which does not include your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies often use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) (link to the NAI universal user opt-out).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with my site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

I have no access to or administration abilities over any cookies that are used by any advertisers on my site.

Links to Other Websites

This website may contain links to other sites that are not controlled in any way by me. Please be aware of this when you click on any such links, I am not responsible for the privacy practices and/or policies of any website other than my own. Consequently, I strongly suggest that you review the privacy policy of every website you visit, whether or not they are linked to you by my site.

Registration and Use of Personal Information

Registration is not required in order to use or access this website.

Security

I follow accepted industry standards to protect any personal information you have provided to me. However, please be aware that no method of electronic storage can ever be 100% secure. Therefore, as is the case with any organization, I am not in a position to guarantee the absolute security of your information.

You may submit any questions you may have about our security procedures by emailing me at couponingfor4 (at) gmail (dot) com

Legal Disclaimer

I reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when I believe that disclosure is necessary to protect my rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process served on my website.

Contact Details

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, or you wish to contact me please email me at:

couponingfor4 (at) gmail (dot) com

This privacy policy was last updated on March 20, 2011.
